Guide to the Freedom to Marry Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Evan Wolfson Files, 1948-2009; Series I; 20.5; (44 boxes)
  - Research files, 1983-2007
    - The Democratic party, 'moral values' and gay rights: the marriage of politics and principle (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Economic reports (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Family Law Quarterly volume 40 number 3, 2006 Fall (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - First Amendment: "Adult" shops New York City (Manhattan Borough President) task force, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - First amendment - Parades Hurley (Boston), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - First Amendment constitutional rights AIE v. Thornbrush (phonesex), 1991 October (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - First Amendment constitutional rights GAVG v. city assessor, city of Rochester, New York, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - First Amendment constitutional rights National Gay Task Force (NGTF) v. Oklahoma, 1984 December (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - First Amendment Holtzman v. Grievance Committee (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Geographic trends among same-sex couples in the United States census and the American community survey, 2007 November (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Hispanic and Latino same-sex couple households in the United States, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Insurance (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Holtzman (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Iowa (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - The momentum report - 2007 edition (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - The money behind marriage amendments, 2007 January 27 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - National gay and lesbian task force: same-sex marriage initiatives and lesbian, gay and bisexual voters in the 2006 election (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - The origins of the distinctiveness of lesbians, gays, and bisexuals in American politics, 2007 August (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - People v. Leberla legal brief (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Photographs (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Red families v. blue families, 2007 August 16 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Report of Vermont commission on family recognition and protection, 2008 April 21 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Same-sex couples and the gay, lesbian, bisexual population: New estimates from the American community survey, 2006 October (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Sandra Cote-Whiteacre and others [FNI] vs. Department of Public Health and others [FN2] SJC-09436, 2006 March 30 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - SC-Tribe Genetics institute and Chugai v. Amchen briefs, 1991 August 27 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - State of New York v. Robert Uplinger and Susan Butler, 1983 October (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Supporting marriage equality: findings from the evaluation of civil marriage collaborative, 2004 January (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - The Third Way Culture project, 2007 April (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Unequal under the law, 2007 October (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Villanova public law and legal theory working paper series, 2008 April (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Where the Democratic candidates stand (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Winning marriage: what we need to do, 2005 June 21 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - 'Wrongful death' Leigh Jones paper, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - 2007 State of the states report (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - The 2008 presidential candidates' positions on lesbians, gay, bisexual and transgender issues (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Administrative Records, 2005-2011; Series II; .5; 2 boxes
  The bulk of series II, Administrative Records, is closed until 1 January 2035 per the collection's deed of gift. Materials in box 45 cannot be accessed without permission from the donor until 1 January 2035.
  The Administrative records series contains incorporation documents and records pertaining to day-to-day running of Freedom to Marry, as well as office documents and material regarding staffing and procedures.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - 501c3 application - IRS questions (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Astraea, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Astraea Foundation, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Blackberry (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - C3/C4 issues (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Federal lobbying registration (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Freedom to Marry incorporation 501c3 checklist (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - File folder labels (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Job applicants, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - National Space Tour, 2011 March 15 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - National Space Tour, 2011 April 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - National Space Tour, 2011 May 4 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Original 501c3 filing with the IRS (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Original C3 incorporation - with New York (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Report, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Development Files, 2003-2012; Series III; 3.5; 7 boxes
  Material in boxes 48-53 cannot be accessed without permission from the donor until 1 January 2035, per the collection's deed of gift. Box 47 is open to researchers.
  The Development Files series contains annual reports, donor information and meeting minutes and other documents pertaining to donor relations.
  The Development Files is organized in two groupings: annual reports, and donor files.
  - Annual reports, 2003-2008
    - 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - 2007 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Donor files, 2003-2012
    - Alphabetical donations
      - Fiscal year 2008 A-I (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Fiscal year 2008 J-R (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Fiscal year 2008 S-Z (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Fiscal year 2009 A-I (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Fiscal year 2009 J-R (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Fiscal year 2009 S-Z (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Anne R. Dow Family Foundation 07-08, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Arcus
      - 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - 2010 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Foundation, 2003 April-2005 May (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Grant, 2012 February-March (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Astraea
      - 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Budget, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Fiscal sponsorship agreement (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Broadway cares, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Broadway cares, 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Calamus (Pend), 2008 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Canela Foundation, 2012 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - CMC, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Columbia
      - 03-04, 2001-2003 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - 04-05 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - 05-06 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - 06-07 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - 07-08 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - 08-09 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Deer Creek 04-05 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Deer Creek (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - E-giving fundraising, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Events
      - Art for Equality, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Fiftieth birthday celebration, 2006-2007 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Wed Rock D.C., 2004 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Wed Rock Los Angeles, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Wed Rock New York, 2004-2006 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Ford Foundation, 2012 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Funders for lesbian + gay issues, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Gill
      - 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Action Fund Freedom To Marry, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Foundation, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Foundation, 2009-2010 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Foundation #12368, 2001-2008 (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
    - Haas, Jr. Fund
      - 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Maltz, David, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - MN United for All Families, 2012 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Movement advancement project, 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Movement advancement project, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Movement advancement project, 2008-2009 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - Movement advancement program miscellaneous materials, 2009 October (Box 51, Folder 3-5)
    - Movement advancement project: CFO conference, 2006 December 8 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) of California, 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Nathan Cumming, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - National collaborative, 2008 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Open Society Institute
      - 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous materials, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Overbrook
      - 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - 2009-2010 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - 2010 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - 2012 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Pagnoni, Laurence A., 2005 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller brother fund miscellaneous materials, 2003-2005 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Small Change
      - 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - 2005-2005 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Stonewall Community Foundation, 2005-2010 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Ted Snowdon
      - 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - 2009-2010 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Tides Foundation FTM, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Tides/John Lee Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Tides/John Lee Fund, 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Vanguard Endowment, 2008-2009 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Vanguard Endowment, 2010-2011 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Vanguard, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Wellspring
      - 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 15-16)
      - Advisors (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Advisors, 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Advisors, 2009-2010 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Advisors, 2012 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Program Files, 1973-2016; Series IV; 45.84; 113 boxes
  Program Files (Series IV) has three levels of access per the collection's deed of gift. Materials in boxes 54-92 are open to researchers. Materials in boxes 93-157 cannot be accessed without permission from the donor until 1 January 2035, and materials in boxes 158-160 cannot be accessed until 1 January 2035.
  Additionally, boxes 82-92 and 131-157 are audiovisual materials. Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  The Programs series covers programs that were run by, funded by, or partnered with Freedom to Marry. This includes schedules, pamphlets, communications, publications, partner organization files, and contains some regranting material that was not included in the Regranting series because it includes more information on the partner organizations. Evan Wolfson material that is included in this series is material about Wolfson, and not his professional papers.
  The Program files also contain captures of Freedom to Marry's internet presence, which includes social media, the official Freedom to Marry website, and videos produced by Freedom to Marry. Not included are state-level sites for Freedom to Marry.
  The Programs series is organized in seven groupings: Subject files, Campaign files, Clippings, Polling files, Communication files, Partner organization files, Publications, and Internet and social media. This series is organized primarily chronologically, with the exception of the Clippings grouping and the Polling files grouping, which are organized chronologically.
  - Subject files, 2002-2015
    - AARP - National Association of Black Journalists (NABJ), circa 2005 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Biweekly calls, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Bourgeois prints follow-ups, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 3-7)
    - "California Marriage and Beyond Marriage" strategy meeting, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - "Californians for Civil Marriage: Survey Repost", 2002 June 10 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Coalition meeting notes steering committee, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Conference programs, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Contracts with vendors, 2009-2015 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Creating change, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Decision Resources Ltd. 2011 project 315: State of Minnesota Residential Survey, 2011 March (Box 54, Folder 2-4)
    - Department workplan, 2004-2006 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Defense of Marriage Act (DOMA), 2004 (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
    - Eight: The Mormon Proposition, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - En Espanol web project, circa 2005 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Evan travel meeting notes, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Evan Wolfson advice to candidates, 2003 November (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Evan Wolfson - articles drafts, circa 2004 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Evan Wolfson correspondence, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Evan Wolfson materials
      - 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Blueprint, "All Together Now", circa 2001 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Clipping and photographs, 2007 (Box 79)
      - DVD reel communications, 2005-2006 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Wolfson's op-eds, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - 100 prominent NYers, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Group photograph with autograph, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Washington Post op-ed: "No Threat to Marriage", 2003 October 4 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Writing, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Every Family Matters, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Faith, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Faith: God still speaking a marriage, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Faith: United Church of Christ general Synod, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Freedom to Marry goals, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Goodridge vs. the Board of Health, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Hollywood group, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Hollywood group, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Idea development worksheet, 2000-2006 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - International marriage, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Interns/volunteers, 2005 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Invoices, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Juan Barajas
      - Juan Barajas: donor follow-up (Box 94, Folder 22)
      - Juan Barajas: donor lists (Box 94, Folder 23)
      - Juan Barajas: Evan prospects (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Juan Barajas: Hormel grant, 2015 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Juan Barajas user agreement, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Landscape: Connecticut, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Landscape: marriagerights.com, 2006 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Landscape: New Mexico, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Landscape: state 411, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Maps and reports, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Marriage institute, 2006 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Meeting notes/General, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Messaging resources, 2014 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Opposition research: American Family Association, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Opposition: Focus on the family, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Opposition: National coalition of African American ministers, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Outlaw marriages: The Hidden Histories of Fifteen Extraordinary Same-Sex Couples, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - People for the American Way (PFAW), 2006 October 19 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Planning template, 2006 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Political landscape
      - 2005-2006 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Equality California (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Equality Florida, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Marriage landscape info, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Powerpoint, 2007 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - PRO/Budget, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - PRO/Creating change, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Program director - HIRE, 2005 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Program director - resumes, 2005 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Program director - Roey Thorpe, 2006 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Program director: Roey Thorpe press release, 2006 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Program goals and objectives, 2004 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Red Carpet, 2005 April 22 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Research on same sex marriage, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Resources for stars, 2006-2007 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Resources: Stanford study, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - SSM/prospectus, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Senior web producer, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - SimonSays Productions event proposal for Freedom to Marry, 2006 November 7 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Steering committee, 2004-2005 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Steering committee, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Steering committee reports, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Story center, featured families, 2006 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Story center expansion, 2006 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Technical assistance: 1049 films, inc., 2003 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - TED 2012 Attendee packet (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Training
      - Speakers training, circa 2005 (Box 96, Folder 21)
      - Connecticut Speakers Bureau, circa 1994, circa 2003 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Connecticut Speakers Bureau binder, 2013 March 29; 2 (Box 97, Folder 2-3, Box 132, Box 133)
        - Marriage Equality for same-sex couples: A Connecticut Conversation, 2016-M-0049-0001; 1 (Box 132)
        - Marriage Equality for same-sex couples: A Connecticut Conversation, 2016-M-0049-0002; 1 (Box 133)
      - Creating change, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Evaluations, Connecticut, 2003 March 29 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Federation summit, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Liberation conversations, 2005 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - United Church of Christ, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - United Nations delegates dining room, circa 2005 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Volunteers, Liz Galst, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - "Why Marriage Matters", 2005 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - "Why Marriage Matters" publication agreement, 2003 December (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Worth plans 2003 matrix (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - 2006 LGBT movement standard annual report pilot year, 2006 September 26 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - 2012 Marriage briefing flash drive, 1 (Reel 134)
  - Campaign files, 1990-2015
    - National campaign files, 1990-2015
      - #Lovemustwin results, 2015 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - 2005 campaign: Federal marriage amendment (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - 2012 marriage briefing binder, 2012 November 29 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Ackerman, Sara notebooks (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - African American mobilization: California (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - African American mobilization (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Annual report & attachments, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Annual report, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Annual report, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Annual report, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Annual reports, 2010 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Blue state digital project outline/email calendars (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Board meeting, 2015 April 26 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Bryan Chin (Box 158, Folder 9)
      - Budget reports, 2005-2008 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Campaign briefing, one Kalamazoo, 2009; 1 (Box 135)
      - Campaign briefing, protect Maine equality, 2009; 1 (Box 136)
      - Campaign briefing, Washington families standing together, 2009; 1 (Box 137)
      - Census reports by the Task Force (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Comm. staff issues (Box 158, Folder 10)
      - Comm. association/executive assistant hire (Box 158, Folder 11)
      - Deutsch, Jo: federal program
        - 2014 (Box 98, Folder 5)
        - #lovemustwin (Box 98, Folder 6)
        - Amicus brief (Box 98, Folder 7)
        - Bad amendments + bills (Box 98, Folder 8)
        - Bills (Box 99, Folder 1)
        - Congressional briefings (Box 99, Folder 2)
        - Cosponsers: background (Box 99, Folder 3)
        - Co-sponsers: respect for marriage act, 1996-2016 (Box 99, Folder 4)
        - Courts, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 5)
        - Defense of marriage act, 2011-2012 (Box 99, Folder 7)
        - DCI group, 2011-2012 (Box 99, Folder 6)
        - Elected officials guide, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 9)
        - Democratic National Convention platform, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 8)
        - Election, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 10)
        - Employment Non-Discrimination Act (ENDA), 2013-2014 (Box 99, Folder 11)
        - Freedom to Marry, 2014 (Box 99, Folder 12)
        - Freedom to Marry (Box 158, Folder 12)
        - Freedom to Marry backgound, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 13)
        - Grassroots/Respect for Marriage Act (RMFA), 2011 (Box 99, Folder 14)
        - Hearing - house judiciary subcommittee, 2011 April 15 (Box 99, Folder 16)
        - Haltaway, 2011 (Box 99, Folder 15)
        - Hearings house and senate files: senate hearing, 2011 July 20 (Box 100, Folder 1)
        - Legislation - 113th session (Box 100, Folder 2)
        - Lush (Box 100, Folder 3)
        - Mayors for (Box 100, Folder 4-6)
        - Mayors amicus brief (Box 100, Folder 7)
        - Mayors (Box 56, Folder 2)
        - Mayors for the Freedom to Marry video release forms (Box 56, Folder 3)
        - Miami event (Box 100, Folder 8)
        - Obama (Box 100, Folder 9)
        - Polling press conference, 2011 July 27 (Box 100, Folder 10)
        - Respect for Marriage Act (Box 100, Folder 11)
        - Respect for Marriage Coalition (Box 101, Folder 1)
        - Salon (Box 101, Folder 2)
        - Social security (Box 101, Folder 3)
        - Southerners for (Box 101, Folder 4)
        - White House (Box 101, Folder 5)
        - Windsor decision (Box 101, Folder 6)
        - Work notes/quill notepad (Box 101, Folder 7)
        - Work notes/yellow spiral bound notebook (Box 101, Folder 8)
        - Young Conservatives (Box 101, Folder 9-10)
        - Young Conservatives for the freedom to marry media training packet (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - Young Conservatives for the freedom to marry messaging documents (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Deutsch, Jo: LGBT federal legislative retreat binder (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Elected officials (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - End of year campaign results, 2014 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Executive assistant search (Box 158, Folder 13)
      - Freedom to Marry annual report, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Freedom to Marry event Los Angeles selects, 2012 July 10; 1 (Box 82)
      - Freedom to Marry OCEC - marriage matters, 1 (Box 83)
      - Freedom to Marry promotional material (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Freedom to Marry selects photos by Maria Schriber, 2012 April 12; 1 (Box 84)
      - Freedom to Marry Sseliskar photography, 2012 October; 1 (Box 85)
      - Freedom to Marry Week
        - General, 2003-2005 (Box 56, Folder 8)
        - Media, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 9)
        - Press (Spanish): general, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 10)
        - Press (Spanish): brochures/in development, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 11)
        - Press (Spanish): brochures in English, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 12)
        - 2006 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - 2007 (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - 2007 (Box 57, Folder 3)